What's going on, Nate? Congratulations.
Uh
did you have any idea the Jaguars were
interested in you?
Uh man, I I I I talked to to the Titans
coach a little bit. Um
but yeah, I didn't go on any visits or
anything like that.
Didn't have a a formal with them. So, I
guess I didn't know, but um I couldn't
be happier.
What was your reaction when you saw the
the number pop up on your phone?
You know how it is. It's with the with
the spam stuff coming up. I saw um a
random number. It said spam on there,
and and uh I didn't know what to do. I
showed my agent. He said, "Better answer
it." And so,
uh so I answered it. And in my heart
sank. Um
man, it's crazy.
Well, I'm sure you're glad you answered
it. Congratulations, man. Welcome to
Jacksonville.
Appreciate it.
We'll go to Demetrius followed by Ryan.
Hey Nate, congratulations. Um just in
terms of of how you might fit with the
Jaguars, how do you feel about the fit?
And have they talked to you at all about
what they plan for you?
Yeah, I I was just talking to coach, and
he said he's really excited to uh get me
in there and talk personnel, uh for
sure. Um
you know, yeah, I'm just excited to get
in there and learn and and um prove
myself. And I think I got a long way to
go. I got a I got a high ceiling, and
I'm ready to go prove it.
For uh maybe Jaguar fans who who don't
really know much about your game, how
how would you sell yourself to them?
Yeah, I I think I'm a a physical
physical blocker. Uh I like to put my
face in the fan. Uh I get in there and
get physical and and and play through
the whistle. And I think I have a lot of
potential in the passing game. Um I've
I've made big plays in my career. Um I
haven't always had the most production,
but um you know, when the ball comes my
way, usually usually been able to
capitalize.
Awesome. Congrats again.
Appreciate it.
>> Hey Nate, Ryan from the Times-Union here
in town. Uh that one year at Texas A&M,
what'd you like about the offense and in
the way you used you and how that may
prepare you for the NFL?
Yeah, I love that offense. That was a
big reason why I went there. Um very
versatile offense, kind of pro style. We
did did a lot of things. Um we moved the
tight ends around. Uh we had a lot of
weapons. Uh Casey, you know, Mario, all
those guys. Um
and so, yeah, I wasn't, you know, a
main, you know, threat in the passing
game, but uh like I said, we had a very
versatile offense. I had a massive uh
route tree for the tight end. So,
um I absolutely loved it. I think it was
a great offense, and and I think I
thrived in it. Yeah, advice to me is
starting off as a walk-on now being a
second-round pick. Um what kind of pride
do you take in this journey?
Uh it's absolute dream come true. Um
it's the best day of my life. It it's
just uh
um brings me back to all the all the the
6 years of college football and, you
know, and high school football and just
working towards this dream and this
goal, and it's and it's finally come.
All right. Thanks, buddy.
Thank you.
Uh D-Rock followed by Mark Long.
Hey Nate, did you think you'd be taken
this so early in the draft? Or what what
were your expectations um maybe going
into the draft?
Yeah, honestly, I I had no idea. Uh I
didn't really want to know. Um
my agents [snorts] kind of kind of kept
out of that because they know it's a
slippery slope with that. Uh draft is
kind of an animal house. There's a lot
of uh
a lot of stuff, you know, unexpected
happens. So, honestly, the way I saw it,
I just wanted to uh sit back and enjoy
the ride, and and uh and I'm having a
great time now.
Thank you.
Hey, congrats. Uh
first off,
are you where are you watching it?
Where did you watch the draft from? And
how many people? And kind of what was
the reaction like initially
when you heard your name?
I was with with my uh with my family. Um
my fiance, my fiance's family, and my
agents. Uh we kept it pretty low-key. Um
very special moment. Um
yeah, it's insane.
Are you in Nebraska? Where you at?
Yeah, we're in uh in Gretna, Nebraska,
where my parents live. Yes, sir. Okay.
And then secondly, you said you got a
lot of upside.
What do you What do you think that is in
terms of pass-catching ability? You feel
like you were underutilized in that in
that role?
Uh yeah, absolutely. Um
so, I I got a lot better, especially in
my last year at A&M, at winning a man. I
think that's something that I I um you
know, improved at a lot, and I have a
long way to go. I I think I can
obviously uh keep improving in that
area. And I have good hands and a and a
and a big catch radius. Um just a big
body making it.
All right, we'll end with Mia.
Hey Nate, congrats. Um not only were you
a walk-on in at Nebraska, but obviously
the walk-on program at Nebraska, huge
tradition.
Just describe for you your football
journey from when you were a young kid
playing at Nebraska, probably achieving
a lifelong dream, and now obviously
getting drafted into the league.
Um I'm sorry, I couldn't hear you for
the first like three quarters of that.
Can you repeat that? Sorry. Yeah, let's
try that again. Um walk-on walk-on
Nebraska. What does it mean to be a
walk-on at Nebraska, assuming for you as
a kid growing up there, that meant a
lot, and now to be here on the precipice
of your NFL dreams?
Yeah, I mean, I grew up in a small town
in Nebraska. Um always was a a
Cornhusker fan. Um man, that was a dream
come true going to Nebraska as a
walk-on. Uh my brother was there as a
walk-on. Um
like I said, we grew up a Nebraska fan,
so it was it was cool going there. And
they have such a rich walk-on program.
Um and I got there with my tight ends
coach, Coach Sean Beckton, and he just
helped me improve so much. He built a
foundation for me, and I it really took
me a long way.
Last question for me. Uh a clip was just
sent to me. You did go against Travis
Hunter when he was at Colorado. Do you
remember anything from that game?
Uh absolutely. Yeah, I did. Yeah. That's
awesome.
Uh you remember anything from that from
that game in particular?
Yeah, I do. Um he ended up ripping my
helmet off.
Um
I'm excited to uh you know, talk to him
about that. I just remember him being
super cool about it, though. Um I
remember blocking him a few plays later,
and we were we were bros again. So,
um I'm excited to meet him and and uh
you know,
figure all that out.
Congrats. Thanks, Nate. See you soon.
Thank you. Appreciate it.